Couple of minutes we are starting with the
new stream link
ok let's play you can
start here we go three to one everyone is
strong tallying semi-final first match make some noise
great listening and what a sound first
ball into the block hole what a start
so semi-final one started n dazzlers
vs pink panthers pink panthers the toss
elected to field
first eight over
match semi-final one Rahul Panchal and Mitesh
Chauhan the opening pair n m aleela hai per
cadre two balls ball two for no
loss single run
heard Mitesh Chauhan
strike toss scored wide umpire miss
after three balls fon lo n dazzlers ah
swing miss just off line wide
umpire f bo
ic lade broke premier league
20 r na entered into the semi-final round
first semi-final in progress n l v
pink panthers
four balls six runs no wicket
and first wicket excellent catch taken after
first wicket fall of n dazzlers
five balls six runs one wicket
good catch taken by vikas vikas dev
team  Diya hai
five balls ch par ek so
five balls bo siv a dazzler new batsman
Siddhesh More all-rounder from n
dazzlers fielder der at wad
langgan single
run so single to end of the over good start
from Pink Panthers one waggun from frav a n
dazzlers
and
so very good start from Hemant Ambekar
back to back three dots into the block
hole n
dazzlers n p 37 fav n
dazzlers kung shot l gall the way
sir tremendous
sixer across for a run straight
into the constellation a de ch 1 on n
dazzlers Siddhesh More strike well well
lang n f
six looking to play over covers got
outside edge only single run
IC Labad Brokers Premier League 205 Day
Two Season
Two Very good shot alti palti de ghuma ke
jio player wahe wahe cha run for four runs
this is the end of the over after two overs a
dazzlers season two day two end event sporting
partner Brand NEX
Media
2. Match Semi-Final One in Progress
2.1
1941 Na Parshuram New
bowler Parshuram Parshuram
V bowling left round wicket S field
two D two 20 par one N Diesels Semi-Final
One Who will win and go enter the final
Which team will enter the final Four Big Contenders
in the Semi-Finals
2.3 21 Fav N
Diesels Something Different Something
Special Mitesh
Yohan 2.4 241 N Diesels
So very good field there
so single to end of the
over No 25 a single
Mitesh Chan bang a fo and side More 13
of 10 with one maximum
hit three overs 25 par one
[Music]
It's very well played T Gun bowler The fielder is
running but ball wins the race cracking
boundary T signal by umpire
3.3 32 par one N
Diesels 3.3 32 Fav has
played this time and the ball goes over the
boundary  Outside off,
back to back
boundaries for four runs, nice boundaries from Mitesh
Chauhan,
good bowling from Vikash
Shukla,
late four overs, game over at 37, one N
Dazzlers
semi-final one in progress, ICC Lord
Bucks Premier League
2025 Day Two Now, we have entered in the semi-final
game,
bowling, Pratik Kadam,
bowling, all the way to Pratik Kadam, one
over, one seven runs, one
wicket, 4 N Dazzlers,
Siddhesh
More, but he is well inside the
crease, very good running, quick
running, quick running by Mitesh
Chauhan 4.2 39 Fw N Dazzlers, very
good bowling, will they come back for two bit
of miss
field, 4 Path 41 Fw N Dazzlers, coming back
for two
more runs, taken by Siddhesh
More, sish more Mitesh
Chauhan 4.4 44 Fw N Dazzlers, initially Pink Path,
the toss elected to bowl first and they all but
first very good shot, excellent timing,
shot for a run, all the way  De Ghuma ke four runs
4 D Pa 48 fw Mitesh Chauhan is doing wonders
25 12 balls four
fours
4548 last ball five over very
good and follow through by Pratik Kadam
late bowl two v 17 for one after fours 49
fw N Diesels
after five overs 49 f one A and
Diesels five overs 49 one five and back 49 one
wicket score
very big shot played in the gap
no fielder
or covers present there the in field f four
runs and with this four runs completes 50 runs A
Diesels 5.1 53
Mitesh Chauhan doing something special in this
match 30 of 14 with f
fors cracking shot no fielder or the fielder
this time to stop mid wicket region for couple
of runs
taken 32 15 with f fors 5.2 55 N
Diesels we can
predict 80
plus to clears infield  T will take the way
fast F for
runs Cracking boundaries Mitesh
Chauhan Absolute Fantastic Pushpa will not bow down
and Mitesh will not stop, no
5359 A Ls has been
sent this time and
back to back conceded boundaries in the mid-wicket region
40 of 17 with San
Phos was batting brilliantly there
Mitesh N Dazzlers 63 four
clean
bowled Excellent bowling
finally Para
labor he got success A very well played
by
Mitesh 40 of 18 balls F hit the ball across the seven seas
Seven
fours Strike of 22.22
5.5 63 for two So the
over will end with two runs
After six overs 65 for two A on Dazzlers Now
how many runs will Gautam and Siddhesh make in the coming two overs
Six overs 65 A on Dazzlers
and this ball went very high Cameraman
catch Absolute Fantastic T Fent like rocket
S into the cloud into the galaxy Six
runs broke the earth  6.2 29 Pttu Siddhesh
More is interested in only delivering big hitting no need for single he will cover all the runs in maximum hitting
6.3 79 Pttu comes back for two runs 16 runs so far in these overs four balls bowled 6.4 81 Pttu last two balls coming up off the last over spare only single run 6 runs the last ball of seventh over coming up Gautam on strike Palen bowled ld goal batsman got clean bowled after
seven overs 82 Pttu three Pttu Siddhesh More is interested in only delivering big hitting no need for single he will cover all the runs in maximum hitting 6.3 79 Pttu comes back for two runs 16 runs so far in these overs four balls bowled 6.4 81 Pttu last
two balls coming up off the last over spare only single run 6 runs the
last ball of seventh over coming
up Gautam on strike
Palen
bowled ld goal batsman got clean
bowled after seven overs 82 Pttu three Pttu
takes
Sen judged run 82 for the
Praneeth  Parab and Siddhesh
More these two are on fire these two Pushpa on
fire over 82 Pati now the last over this first
innings semi-final
one only
single second semi-final coming up
MIBL vs Howden
captain ready for the
toss MIBL vs Howden the semi-final
to MBL captain Howden captain ready
for the
toss we are waiting for the Howden captain it's
very good fielding ud maar fielding
performance by Pratik More 7.3 843 A
Diesel's last three balls first innings
it's been given wide outside off
line 853 N
Diesel's it's taken very well catch taken by
Ramesh so very well played Sish More 30 off 21
balls and it's
six looking to clear the long off region
and it's long off take the
catch
7.4 85 Pe four Kiski hogi jeet aur kiski hogi haar
N Diesel
going for two runs in the direction of Swee
And it's out run
out very good throw
So Pritesh it's good throw from  sleak
region
7.56 f f now the last ball of the first
innings
icicic lord brokers premier league
semi final
one adelo vs pink panthers final
ball
now swing that
ball is out stumping out so a gun 86 s
Pink Panthers
need 87 runs to win fun enter so the
target for Pink Panthers to
chase so we'll take a short break and come back
semi final first is on in
the game of life stay protected with
icic lord ers
junk food raise
energy low
in the game of life stay protected with
icic lord health insurance pa
[music]
in the game of life stay protected with
icic lord health insurance
[music]
jump food
raise energy
low in the game of life stay protected with
icic lord health insurance
pa
[music]
to one make some strong tally semi final
one second innings we start the target 87 chase
first ball very good shot boundary line ke bahar
yeh gayi first
ball
strike
first ball for pratik kadam  Non
strike and Ankur Jan starts the
affair already started with from An
Diesel for four runs on the first ball the fielder went to deep at cover he turned the ball
and the fielder
turned a little on the other side
two balls eight runs due to dew factor the
fielder turned the ball back to back
for a cut boundary it
just leg stump out leg stump for a white
ball two balls nine runs good start Pink
Panthers
Vishram has made the opposition team
cautious
this
time in the gap there
Messi and Ronaldo were trying to
stop him with their football
skills but it went out
in the gap three balls 13 runs Pink Panthers will
start firing start target 87 runs
this time trying to hit big shots over the stumps after four
just ball 1 for no loss IC
Lord Brocks Premier League semi-final one
in progress 87 target given by Els to
Pink Panthers takes
a cheeky
cut but the fielder was at
short third
man fi balls bowled 14 for
Last ball coming up of the first
over the current 16 record just 10 catches taken
fantastic was long Ankur Jan Sen
number jersey thala for
region no the
magic looking for the big one and
gone so good come back by Ankur the bowler 14
runs conceded but this important
wicket wicket Prateek Kadam caught Rajit bowled
Ankur first ball pakistan kadam got
so Vishram still in the
crease one over 14 for one over 14 for one
Pink Panthers
Siddhesh More
all-rounder batted well the first innings 30
of 21 and
26 now with the
ball so one more power play only to feed out
side circle is allowed one feed
deep extra
cover not
long good fielding good thu nili single
run 1 pv
152 not out coming
6.5 new man Ramesh
Suresh ka saath chhod ke aaye in batting
Ramesh very good
bowling it's the advantage of being a high
bowler you read the  Batsman completely and put
the pressure on maintain the line and
length 1.2 f one Pink Panthers
good stopper outside edged shot to third man
region
1.31 f one Pink Panthers
score is Pink Panthers now in
danger score is 17
70 runs needed 6.3 overs left 70 runs
balls had he shot directly could have got some wickets
at the non-striker's end but not taking the risk if one run is lost
1.41 f one Pink Panthers
69 to get from coming 38
balls Siddhesh More very good bowling four
balls four
runs absolute good
bowling the first end 14 runs good come back
from an dazzlers
five balls five singles
1.5 f
one swing miss down the track looking to play
for the big
one and their connection did not work seems their
match has not happened bumble on no 19 Pink Panthers after to
19 f one Pink Panthers 68 runs coming  36
balls to the right of the pads. Maximum can be reached in the
side circle. Four fielder should be inside
circle. Mandatory non-power play.
Pranit Parab comes on strike. Vishram
plays it lightly towards the pads. Steals a single.
2. 67 to get from coming on. 5.5 35
balls 67 runs. The required run rate is around
11.50. Plays towards wide long on for a
single. 2.
66 runs left.
34 balls left. The fielder fails to catch it. The
ball goes outside the boundary for four.
Top edged and sent for four at the backward region. 2.
62 runs off 25. 33 balls current
10 and required is
11.27. It's a very good
shot. Six runs into the commentary box. Bang
on the
roof. Excellent sixer from
Vishram. 27. 11 balls, four fours and a
maximum.
Hit 2. 4 31 balls.  Pink
Panthers looks to cut it, the ball bounces a little
and goes into the hands of the keeper 2.5 31
good bowling this time signals a wide ball
2.5 32 fw 55 fm
31 reverse hit straight field at short
third man he will take strike single at end of
the over
Three overs over play is over 33 fw Pink Panthers
54 no required from four overs
left After three overs 33 fw 33 One
wicket 54 In five overs
Rahul Panchal comes to bat
3 One
wicket Catch Catch T Catch T And he
took a good catch at corner
region catch Fun
Matches Rahul Panchal will blast on the first ball
Catch taken by Gautam He is not Gambhir
33 for
two New batsman coming at number four
Hemant still in this match N
Diesel and Pink Panthers and this big
wicket 28 14 balls four fours one six
excellent batting performance once again strong
tally F Vishram Sak very well played
Batting is by Hemant Ambekar Naveen
Palandaj
3.1 33
ft Sco outside edge Only single at third
man Shot to third man
fielder 3.2 34 ft 53 runs Now
20 8 balls
left So now current done and required is
almost 7 10.20 and
11.36 Just one acceleration of one run to get
Current and required
same You tried this
time I would go more to three steps back You can even take a
catch But quick reflexes are very
much
required He tried to take that but went over for four
runs 3.3 38 ft Pink Panthers 49 to get and
coming 27
balls Good shot by
Ramesh T played towards cow corner region for
four
Just shot of Siddhesh in the field at long
of two runs taken 4 ft
3.4 47 runs to get from 26
Now shot once  Again lucky the batsman
is good stopped at the long off
region only a single run this time 3.5 41
from two very close encounter close
chance swing and miss dot bal t end of the
over so t end 41 phat four over left 46 to get ic ic
longboard Brokers Premier League
Season Two Day Two Event Sporting Partner
Brand Next Media
It's a great first day and also now the second
day super exciting super Sunday Funday Now we are at the
semi-final round the
first semi-final
progress back to back Praneeth Praneeth doing
something magical bowling now
46 from 3.4
now very good catch excellent taken sir running
catch from long
off and very good catch taken late so wicket no. 1
Ramesh
Depart 10 of 10 bal 4
dti 41
fth completely here in this match both
teams and 5050 equation chances of
win let's see now one quality over and one
big over n dazzlers
Let's see Pink Panthers can make something
special now the new batsman
Pratesh Pawar on strike
takes an outside chance for the keeper to take that.
Batsman
survives 45 from 20.
Now excellent bowling from Pranpradesh
Parab last ball of this over
Praneet and what is left here, the dream is shattered.
43 runs after five overs. Needed 44 runs in the next three overs
and this seamer is outside off for four.
5 47 not 40 runs 16
[applause]
[music]
Balls 40 runs 16
balls swinging
well here n dazzlers have
kept a good hold and bowled well.
15 runs
40 15 balls 40 runs
47 not 40 from 14
balls 40 from 14 balls
the passing marks of 40 14 once
again Rahul
Panchal very good
bowling 40 runs now 1 ball a big hit will do
something amazing and will do something amazing Hemant
and
Pritesh More goes into the commentary box
very good fielding by him beyond the boundary
line for four
runs so six overs go 51 for two overs
left 36 to get a cracking shot long off
for four icy
aasi labad rokas premier league
25 season two day
two even sporting partner brand next
media so
good bowling Siddesh More now into at
36 now from 11 balls
only single
run so 35 from 10
balls 3.5 every
ball once again swing
miss Siddhesh More turning the
change of the course of the match
three
balls only one
run in the innings so far 35 not from nine
balls once again swing miss
to screen bowl let bails go good bye tata bye
6.5
524 Siddhesh More on
strike 6 today 52 for
four and 35 runs now needed in seven balls
so couple of runs and that will be the end of number
sent to 54 f end  They require 33 to get into the
final
over still the discussion is on who will be the man
of the match Mite Chauhan has played well 4 for 18
from More 21 with
14 26 off Siddhesh More took one more wicket
wicket also
so coming up final over
of semi final one a Dazzlers
will enter into the final
single looking for to deep extra
cover and they will go
for one more
run going back for fourth run
and
gun so three runs taken from
Amey so now n Dazzlers will be the first
contender to enter into the final
33 five balls need 30 runs and this dot ball
with this
n Dazzlers
final me karenge entry aur unko hum
puchhenge final match or perform what is
happening swing a
miss 7.3 57 on
five 30 from three so now it's just
time to celebrate the
first finalist here we go
last ball 28 runs required
swiss n Dazzlers entering into the final one
by 27  Runs many much congratulations ic lo
brokes premier league first
finalist
path none
dazzler error from my side rectified an
dazzler
so a dazzler very much congratulations
l b calling the man of the
match an dazzler this is
baazigar come quickly come to the match Siddhesh More return return
present ok everyone let Siddhesh
More continue come
Siddhesh More
ji very well
played so make some noise for Siddhesh
more 30 of 21 o ands end with the
bowling two overs a run one
wicket heavy in batting heavy in bowling also
Siddhesh became a bazigar this is jawaas
brilliant explosive
performance so an dazzler entering into the
final coming up the next match
semi final to m
ibl
in the game of life stay protected with
ic lard health insurance
junk food running
in the game of life stay protected with
ic lard health insurance
[music]
jump food colour choice
cracking shot excellent four straight
HM Sports ticket
counter Hello and welcome back once again
ICICI Lombard Brokers Premier League
2025 2nd
semi-final MI BL vs
Howden So MI Bell One The toss elected to
field first after one over single
loss excellent shot last ball of the previous over
four runs very
good catch looking to play for a big one
just
shot an excellent catch taken by him long
not taken by him
Will Yadav this
time unlucky 1.26 How done
new butter Rama
Krishnan first ball looking to play on side got
edge and good call from Mitesh Patil to
take a quick single 1.3 One semi-final in
progress excellent bowling good
bowling turned the match of seven eight overs into a test match
Praful
Navale 1.47 for
Howden all around a ball's Brown Munde how done
batsmen Ramakrishna and Mitesh
Patil one the pa a one how done very
good bowling from Praful just
consider two runs a wicket taken quality
Bowling from
Howden Cliency Bowling from MI BL to
Gun 8 Fav Howden
Lombard Brokers Premier League
2025 Season Two Day Two
Sporting Partner Brand Next
In
Media Sandeep Samal now into the attack
Bar pitched ball outside edge backward
region and single
run 2.49 Fav Howden
outside edge third
man 2 P2 Howden
the fielder to
factor sp
chase yes
gun good
throw
striker MBL the brown Munde done the
job
so 2
P2 Good from Sandeep
late two Dati 11 for two Howden
score now this match come back Howden how will we do
which new batsman is coming
Aniket
Kerkar batting
so 2.4
Done Aniket
looking to play something different ball
well in the different direction opposite
reaction 2.5 Fd Done
thrown outside off line line umpire Mr Om
Singh signalling
wide on this last ball Sandeep Samal mere five
runs aur usko bes diya hai backward  The
fielder tried to hit
it in the region but the ball went away, four
runs, good scoop shot
three and gun 18, fat home
3 the one at 18,
two overs, one ball 18 runs, wicket, how done,
score very good, short pitch ball with Chatra,
attempt to hit big shots but with slow pace it
confused the batsman, good start, here the
bowling unit of MIBL was
successful in taking two wickets.  2 19 pt 2
so we are
back Ramakrishnan let's play towards long n
f
single 3.5
21 f
Howden semi-final two in progress a
game lightly cut
and steals a run
four o' game over 21
[music]
han so 21 psv so four v 22 for two
elegantly played towards point by
Ramakrishnan and single not
taken excellent start here MIBL
team
very well played umpire
checking corner region gets six runs very
well
played
Aniket Kerkar has
4.5 now setting up the big target how done
different type of
shot scoop shot back region catcher's
game over 33 how done
pa 33
's taken very good catch catches catches matches the
third wicket fall how done
MI BL all the Brown Munde Army are
doing a fantastic job yes no yes
no one run
shot so only a single run will count
goes into the block
Whole good bowling Sandeep
Patil 5 off 35 Pati Howden
at taken very good catch Praful 11 ​​number
jersey remember the
name very good catch at long of
region so one fell MI BL striking
well so Sandeep Pal strike for 8 bowled
two runs and two wickets
over and Ramakrishna
depart seven runs 11 balls complete
pressure here semi-final now it will be seen
who comes with a dazzle
finalist second
finalist 5 Da Cha 35 for four
Nimit Vora now new batsman
six overs play over 38 for four How done
good fielding
performance Howden has completely done it
calm all the fielders of IBL
good teamwork good support good
crowd IC Labad Brokes Premier League
2025 semi-final to in progress something
special upper
cut plays two backward region but Ollie single no
6.0 for four How done alti
turnti
shot this is going going
behind the GI lead the
fielder is running to catch the General Insurance
lead and good fielding  There
6.2 42 f
4 6 Dati 42 f f How
done Mani Trivedi and Nimit
Vora let's see how much runs they will add something
to the
board they good bowling unit Arshad Ansari
1.31 runs prof Navle sav sandhi
to total impact on
Howden has completely made this match a
box wicket here MIBL
fielders are
not giving any chance to hit big shots here will go for
two runs ran
fast two runs the
over will end with two runs seven
overs game b 45 f f Coming up final over
of the first innings seven
14 46 for four coming up last five
balls of the first innings
semi-final two
already one finalist entered n dazzlers the
first finalist
so dot ball four ball
left 46 sa the lag two had
very good
bowling good bowling MI BL has
mastered the bowling logistics
inside edge no chance to make any runs here
Quality bowling
performance from MI
BL First ball one run and three dots Last two
balls
this time outside the line White ball SPAY MI
OM
Singh 474 7.4 done
and is out Finally did not get a wicket on non-strike
So got on strike
Two runs and looking for the third run and
gun 49 f f The score
now two balls
the pa 49 f f Coming up last ball of
the first
innings IC Lombard Brokers Premier
League
205 Day
two season To
semi-finals
To so r and go Coming up
last ball first innings Sandeep
Patil into the block hole Very very good
bowling performance Umpire see out
Sling so at gun 49 f s And target to chase
50 runs MIB have to win this match
and enter the finals Will
take a short break Will be back as soon as possible In
the game of life Stay protected
with ICICI Lord Health Insurance
[Music]
J Food
Rising Lo
in the game of life Stay protected with i l
Health  Ins Power D
[Music]
In the game of life stay protected with
world health insurance
and food
[Music]
In the game of life stay protected with
world health
insurance and food
[Music]
So count of
two let's go let's play make some noise once again the
target is 50 in the
over two runs in the first ball two runs in the
field chase down towards the stumps a
couple of overs taken by
Vishal Yadav bowling Harshad Ansari on
strike and Akash Langekar on non-strike
this time he has played defensively good
bowling there by Vishal Yadav
b
target given by me down to me by just a
single at short then
man bo fo lose me by a
block hole good bowling from Vishal
Yadav signalling leg
butt one over is over seven
runs needed in seven overs 43 runs needed in seven overs
IC Brokes Premier League
2025 semi-final two in progress final
ready one team has entered n dazzlers
now this match  Whoever wins will play the final with an dazzler.
Now Aniket
Kerkar Arshad Ansari
Power place on one more
over Jas Close very close stumps out of the
white say Mr Prashant Ray after a after one was at fur
no loss
MIBL 42 T got from
Sen very good cut shot excellent cut
shot
played in the gap for four runs seamer has sent it outside off
umpire
enjoyed just dancing away the signaling F
fo 1 pv F no loss
MIBL T was something different that one hand
goes to the black foot excellent placement and
steals a run
14 runs no wicket 36 runs fireworks have already started
let's go now it's the turn of Sis F 1.3 14
F no
loss a typical tap shot played in box
cricket single not
taken 1.4 F no loss the
ball went to the backward zone slowly slowly
it went four
1.5 19 no wicket
target of 31 31 runs to be scored now  37 balls Target
is 50
runs needed
31 This time directionless bowling White C
umpire 1.5 fails M IBL
cuts it lightly towards point
and takes a run End of over
After 0 21 for no loss M IBL 29 to get coming
36 balls
to get 21 for no loss
Dead ball Sun B
umpire has declared the ball dead, should be revived
Good
bowling Advantage of being hidden ball
Ramakrishnan relies
on length and troubling the batsman
Two D 1 21 for no loss Will be looking for a wicket
Now Howard's ball is
two D 2 23 runs 27 runs needed now
5.4 will
not be easy to win
Special
fielder short cover F Catching position 0 Stop
the
single Two D 2 No wicket on 57 27
runs needed 33
balls 27 for
and the catch is dropped What was missed, dream
shattered Batsman wanted to play on side S G
top  Edge looking London talking Tokyo he got
top edge
2.5 25
more runs needed 25
runs half the job is done half the rest is left for the night the rest is left for later he has
pulled it brilliantly
and made the ball
round against the seamer these four
umpires are
dancing signalling for four
after three overs there is no wicket on 29 now
21 runs are needed in the coming five overs we will
win this match easily MI BL
very good fielding at long on lee single run
conceded
Vishal
Yadav Ajan the bowling
and three the one 30 runs now no wicket has been taken he has
played it towards mid wicket
one
run now they
can't hurry MI BL 19 runs more
balls left
28 bounces and t's gun
four one bounce into defence Arshad Ansari has done a
great job
for
refreshed he pulled
and t's gun catch taken by
Ramakrishnan previous ball for just one
wicket so very well played Arshad Ansari 15
of 11 balls for
15  Need 26 balls first wicket
badan ae
bl time now to perform i time u join with
finalist n dezal will win and now
chance for m bl to join v l
15 to get from
26 35
3.4 new batsman has come Praful
with two runs in the first ball.  Pa 37 on 1 1
na from
25 single to end of the over four o's game over
38 f one only 12 runs needed
in the next four overs
Ramakrishnan into the
attack white
ball
celebration advance fireworks are going on
on the sky
my way or else
skyway with good timing he has pulled it
and put the ball in the wrong direction towards the final
four so just six runs to get for victory
ABL they will enter into N
L Now on a blank paper we write N L
vs MI B L has
cut in the final point region
4.2
44 J Sir required one big hit and tossed it
well cut to the
point only a
single now they just need five
runs five runs needed to win this match
and enter the final with N
Dazzlers MI
B L team
very good cut
shot no ball no
ball and for that it is
the end of the
match MI B L entering into the
final now coming o final
match a  MIBL
so the final match will start at
7:30 and before that we will have toss toss
so guys wait MIBL man of the
match who is coming
Praful Praful Praful
so Praful Navale man of the match two overs six runs
one wicket economical bowling
performance also with the bat 12 runs five
balls two
fours make some noise for Praful Navale
best city from smart Mumbai
City ICI Lombard Brokers Premier
League
2025 now two contenders will play the
final match now dazzlers taking up stay
protected with ICICI Lord Health
Insurance
Jump Food Rang
Choice Energy Lo
in the game of life stay protected with
ICICI Lord Health Insurance Power
Restor
[music]
in the game of life stay protected with aaaa
lord health insurance jn
food
ris ng
in the game of life stay protected
with aaaa lord health insurance power
resto b
in the game of life stay protected with
ICICI Lombard Health Insurance
Jump Food
Rang
Ch Energy
Lo In the game of life Stay protected with
Aaaa Lumbard Health Insurance Power Risto
[Music]
In the game of life Stay protected with
Aaaaa Lumbard Health Insurance Power Risto [Music]
Aaaaa Lumbard Health Insurance Power Risto
[Music]
In the game of life Stay protected with
ICICI Lord Health Insurance Power Risto
[Music]
Food
Risng Lo
In the game of life Stay protected with
Aaaaa Lumbard Health Insurance Power Risto
[Music]
Hello and welcome back ICICI Lumbard
Premier League finalists We are ready for the
final match and the two teams are ready to for the
toss A LS vs MIBL So Sunny spin
the coin and who will
call A L will call heads or tails
who will be the toss Ka
Boss is Captain Rahul Panchal and MBL
Captain Akash Lanjekar
All the best Both the teams Sunny spin the coin A LS vs MIBL Captain
Rahul Panchal will call heads or tails Okay so
once the toss you
will bat any reason for  Batting first we
have good batting attack plus bowling attack so
we are planning to score runs
and keep challenging the opponents here ok
about the journey the tournament the whole tournament
about ICS Lombard
management few words to express it's
extraordinary tournament ok and well well
organised well it's very disciplined
tournament so many more to have in
future so the best ICS team thank you so
much I wish you all the best captain Akash
Lanjekar bowling karnar kay kamaal karna wicket
aa kay strategy asana strategy game me daakh tu aa thik hai bowling tolling message full team journey k hoti k excitement crowd kasa hota khub chhan hota
na ekdum bhari p
broker tournament p
na ekdum bhari khub na ok we will the best
so
center level come in some time thank you very much
in the game of
life health insurance
[music]
in the game of life stay protected with
aaaaard health insurance
[music]
in the game of life stay  Protected with
ICICI Lumbar Health Insurance
Junk Food Rang Choice
Energy
Lo In the game of life Stay protected with
Aaaaard Health Insurance Power Risto
[Music]
In the game of life Stay protected with
Aaaaard Health Insurance Junk Food Rang Choice Energy Lo
In the game of life Stay protected
with Aaaaard Health Insurance Power Risto
[Music]
In the game of life Stay protected with
Aaaaard Health Insurance
Jump Food Rang Choice
Energy Lo
In the game of life Stay protected with
Aaaaard Health Insurance Power Risto
[Music]
In the game of life Stay protected with
Aaaaard Health Insurance Jump
Food Rang Choice
Energy
Lo In the game of life Stay protected with
Aaaaard Health Insurance Power Risto [Music] Junk ... [
Music] The
excitement will begin in some time The final
match of the ICC Labour Brokes Premier League
2025 We are in the final stage now The final match of the ICC Labour Brokes Premier League 2025 We are in the final stage now The
final match of the
MIBL MIBL  All the Brown Army
Brown Munde on the field already we are
waiting for the moment for the final match who
will win the trophy who will win the
cup and the two opening batsmen of Dazzlers be
present as soon as possible
so are we going to keep the bat aside and hit with the sword will he
send it across the boundary line there has been a
roar let's start
so coming up final match
m IBL and here we have the two opening
batsmen
two teams for one cup
ok let's play we will have countdown
from 10 now
so here we go everyone present over here we will have
the countdown now with me everyone 10
no 8 sen saks f fur r to one are you ready let's
play let's row first ball final match
first ball captain Rahul
Panchal and the wicket has fallen on the first ball what a
start fantastic absolute
he got
out on the first ball absolute start m IBL Brown
Munde the
final match has got a great start and he has been out
on the first ball
so this  Two teams will now face each other for a cup.
Welcome back once again to the finals of
ICC Lombard Brokers Premier League
2025. N Diesel vs MI BL. The
patient needs medicine and when Jogi needs it. The
patient needs medicine and when Jogi needs it. We are the
worshippers of cricket. When do we need this
tournament?
Make some noise and let's
start. First
ball. First wicket.
Siddhesh P is now the new
batsman. So on the first ball, the captain is
out. Big wicket falls here. Jh pack very
good stop short fine leg.
So F balls bo six F one N
Diesels played defensively. Good start.
Arshad Ansari after one over. Six for one. A
over for one.
Final match eight over game. A Diesels MI
BL must not the gap. Will go for four.
Second boundary of the match.
Previous over. First boundary from
Siddhesh N Mitesh Chauhan. One on one 10.
N Diesels
score now. The fielder is played in the deep point
region for a single.
One on two 11. One A Diesels
good turn. Read here and  Pushed him and
stole a run Siddhesh More 1.31
Feb Final match in
progress Toss won by N Dazzlers elected
to bat set up the big total How will they
challenge M
IBL Short big ball very well Played the
fielder Rat will they come back for
two Very good throw Excellent throw only a
single
run one Dash ch 1 on
one N Dazzlers MBL Good performance Semi
final now two big contenders Who
will win Who will
lose one on one
Sandeep Salmaan will get the last run The
over will end with a dot ball
After two overs 14 Fav N Dazzlers
After the end of the over 14 Fav One N Dazzlers has
played to square leg Two runs
with speed Good running button Wicket with speed Gets
two runs with speed
2 Pav 16
Fav Waiting for hitting for
just two bounds Now 2.11 for
one Played defensively No run on him
Good bowling Arshad Ansari
Very well  Played towards deep x
kaa code th single
run do dati 17 par 1 n
dazzles Mitesh Chauhan and Siddhesh More are batting
Migrants are going on a plane journey Mitesh
and Siddhesh let's send the ball on some plane journey
Waiting for something special in the
final
match Very good bowling this is excellent
bowling MIPL we seen in the semi-final
now performing well in the final
to 2.41 a good start MI BL team
excellent fielding looking for couple of runs
only a single run Good fielding by MBL
team do dati 18 par 1 n
dazzles Excellent bowling Harshad Ansari two overs
10 runs one wicket Good bowling three overs
play over 18 par 1 n
dazzles Siddhesh More Mitesh Chauhan
waiting for their
fireworks Silence before storm
Umpire raises his finger he guns
So second wicket falls n dazzles in trouble now
so cut behind Good work by the wicket
keeper Akash
Su Mitesh Yohan departs 12 na  Ball with two
passes after hitting boundary
gun.  2 for 22,
no new batsman Ranjit
Tatkare, only a single
run MI BA is something special unit,
fielding unit very
strung, everyone has been
silenced 3.3
Excellent bowling, excellent
turn, only a
single 3.4 2 for 24, N Dazzlers,
very good fielding
performance all around, absolutely this is something
special MI
IBL 3.5 2 for 25,
excellent bowling, quicker and good turn,
four overs over, game over 2 for 25, N Dazzlers,
four overs 2 for 25,
now something different has to be done here,
Siddhesh More and Ranjit Tatkare will not sit quiet in the coming four overs, we need some
fireworks, we
need some cracking hits MI BL now let's see Praful now
into the middle,
Ranjit is on
strike, take team keeper misses out,
collect white plus one run, two extra
runs, four overs 27 for 2,
it's time to become heroes, now N Dazzlers, you can do it, come on,
what a fielding performance
Absolutely excellent fielding set by the
captain
4.128 for two MIBL captain Akash
Lanjekar
good fielding setting good start
in this final match he tried to take the
catch he lost something there balance and that
reason catch has been dropped good effort
getting a life there
couple of catches taken couple of catches by
Ranjeet 4 for two 30 two n dazzles
so very good
bowling it's a dot
ball 4.3 342 n dazzles
Green bowled by Karthik
bowling absolute electrifying and
athletic bowling performance Raful
Navali 4.4 for three n dazzlers
completely silenced the crowd here
MIBL's Brown Munde all around
not bowled but low number for
cracking dot will go away let's see no one will let this go he ran
three runs
one run saved for the team three runs taken for
the
team 4 the par 33  3 for
10 Siddhesh
More 12 for 13, a four
Good
bowling, some different
style, good mix and
managed to take a wicket after seeing eight runs Praful Five overs
finished 33rd A Dazzles
Sandeep Patil comes into the attack Five overs 33rd
No
more night, nothing else, some big hits are
awaited here, everyone is waiting for it
Good bowling into the block
hole Excellent
performance 5.13
Outside
edge Fielders are visible everywhere
5.2 Three for 34 A Dazzles
Just a single Good stop Praful and long
on 5 Dati Three for 35 Good fielding
performance MI IBL Brown Army all around A
little bit outside and wide
signaled
by the umpire Three for 36 5
Dati No
Dazzles Excellent catches catches in the
match and these wickets fall Attempts to hit big shots have
completely destroyed the
Brown Army are heavier than brown bread
5.4 Four for 36
A good start A
good fielding unit completely N  The
Dazzlers have been devastated, isn't it? New
bat Praneeth Parab will play a special inning, will do
some fireworks.
5.4 36 F F Now Praneeth Param is the new
batsman. Only a
single. Only four runs in this over and
managed to take a wicket. Sandeep
Patil last ball. Six
overs. What a silence.
Four for 37. N
Dazzlers.
What a thing. They won't let it go. They wo
n't
leave any boundary. Absolutely good fielding
performance here. Kakan region
and fielder takes catch. The Dazzlers'
batsmen are talking all around. What should we
do? What is my fault? What is the
fault of the team? 6 for 1 and now there are
five
wickets. So 39 F F
6.2 Here MI BL has completely
disturbed the batting unit. They have
troubled them. What have they done and
why have they done
it. They will answer for this and will say
when is all this hard work for them. The final match is on. N
Dazzlers MI
BL is all around.  khaub hai
6.3
445 Need Munster looking for the big one Let's see
Siddhesh
Mori inside edge batsman narrowly escapes
Just one
run Something different is the set formula
MIBL
team Only a single
run 6.5 42 Pa on
Diesels There is no answer to them There is no break to them
They have no mode And further you complete something
Only a single Walking
single They have no mode There is no mode ahead
End of the over 435 N
Ls Very good bowling Only six
runs Now coming up the final over of the first
innings
Asia Lombard Rockers Premier League
2025 Final match on
Final match on Par
Fielding is full
on 7 overs 43 F Last over not of the
first swing N
miss Excellent bowling performance
7.1
435 Stopped back I
don't know how many bus stops
MBL has made today They keep
stopping They are
making speed breakers They are making bus stops
Superb Excellent Fabulous
Outstanding 455  7.2 Last
ball, this is what we were looking for, this is what we were waiting for
Siddhesh
strike run The
lion inside him has now awakened
So with this he is trying to complete 50 runs
Once again he hit a powerful blow Very well played for both the teams What
match What final
match 7.3 51 F F Tough fight between two big
contenders
Two runs will definitely be taken here
7.4 53 on five and
diesels Now something decent score on the total
is looking
fine May be the defendable score Now last
two balls coming up Went to
hit a big shot But only a couple
of
runs Will the rocket be weak in the last ball Will he
hit a six in the last ball To
know watch the final match of ICC
Lombard Rokus Premier
League So coming up
now let's go to the last ball First innings Here we go
make some
noise There are
fielders all around
and they have finally dismissed So More
Excellent Once again he hit a powerful blow
for MI
BL What good fielding performance also
Big row  Apple make some noise for n Diesels
they have also batted well so
with this the first innings ends
so after eight overs
5646 and the target is 57 to chase m IBL in
48 balls eight overs we get a short
break we will be back soon
in the game of life stay protected with
aaaa lumbard health insurance
jump food color choice
energy low
in the game of life stay protected with
aaaa lumbard health insurance pa
[Music]
in the game of life stay protected with
icici lumbard health insurance
jump food color choice
energy low
in the game of life stay protected with
aaaa rd health insurance pa rested
[Music]
so with me
everyone to one let's play
strongly let's clap make some noise come
our first ball
captain Rahul Panchal so now
the captain to captain Rahul Pancha to
Akash there was a chance here but only a single
run we will give something different tough fight ah we must see
n Diesel m IBL
both the batsmen  Off-spinner with a single run,
two balls, two runs,
no wicket, target is 57,
first two overs, power play, just
two feeds outside
circle, lightly cut and pushed, one run
stolen,
two feeds inside circle, one is mid-wicket and
one is
Lagan, good
bowling, will give some tough fight, you will have to see,
N
Diesels, final game, final game, pressure,
or has he played it lightly at mid-
wicket, only a single,
so good start and can from a captain,
taking cha, Rahul
Panchal, one over, five runs, no wicket,
MBL needs 52 runs, now 42
balls left, bowling, Siddhesh More,
28, 24 balls, one each,
now they have to do something amazing, take a wicket, will they be
successful or not or will
Harshad and Akash of MI BL show some different magic,
so here it is the turn of A and Diesels as well,
fielding has given a
good start, only five runs
in the first over, pressure on MI, now
1.16 for no
loss, good fielding, good flick shot,
played it to square leg and this is a good
technique, MI  BL
B doesn't want to take the risk, will
play in the gap, will understand, will read and then
break it 1.28 for no loss MI
BL Both the batsmen playing four of four
Akash and Ansari
cracking shot only will get one bounce into the
fence Mumbai City there the cooker whistle rang
excellent shot outside off the seamer
four Akash Lanjkar
captain taking
and once again a big connection and what is this, the
dream is shattered good effort here what is this
four or
not what a
stop b good stop there only two runs
1.4 14 for no
loss captain absolutely brilliant here
Akash
Lanjkar has sent back Simon go back
return
ticket 1.51 for no loss
and this is an excellent
shot and the catch has been dropped can down
b
commentator shot excellent six runs
so in the commentary box what did I miss
and my dream
is shattered so what strike captain taking the charge
Akash Lanjkar
two overs 20
no wickets and Akash Lanjkar has hurt my hand a
what a strike what a batting performance
MI
BL Sensible batting these are good
batsmen 2.2 21 runs No loss 36 now to get
from 5.4 overs Left
single run taken by
Akash 2.3 22 runs MI
BL 35 runs 33 balls
played in the gap made room One bounce into the
fence It went for
four and sent once more to Rekha and
near the boundary Have you got your insurance done
2.4
26 Excellent batting Harshad and Akash No
wicket yet they will
chase Chasing the target of 57 Just 30 not to
get 31 balls Left
single to end of the over Excellent start Three
overs 28 but no wicket Now
need 29 runs in the coming five overs
27 Now from 26
28 and here
Akash is going for the second wicket
Excellent running between the wickets
back to
back
3.32 no
loss Good fielding
late short extra
cover 25 runs Now 26
balls and here misfield and one rung is taken and he
runs fast  With the second
run, the captain is batting well, taking the
charge 23 and 15 14 and 16 Arshad Ansari takes a
wicket with 14 for 3.5 34 no loss MI
BL 23 runs from 25
balls, clears the
infield, very good
stop at deep extra
cover Akash, the captain has done fireworks today,
four overs over, no wicket on 36,
four overs to play, 21 to
get, will easily complete this match after
four
36 cracking shot, like this, for
excellent shot four
runs Arshad
Ansari striking the well, striking
straight down the ground
for 4.1 44 no loss 17 to
get Gautam Gokhale
ball suddenly changed the time, changed the emotions,
changed the life
4.3 42 15 runs now
to lift the cup MI BL
good effort,
and he saved
so good athletic work fielding done
at the point
region, so the over ends with a single Five
overs 45 12  Runs needed in the coming 18 balls
Only 12 required to lift the trophy
of ICICI Lombard Brokers Premier
League 2025 Season Two
5.15 Just 12 to hit big to win the
match and will go for four
Arshad Ansari and Akash Lanjekar
Rest of the team members are eating comfortably He is
chilled in gout, both of them are
quite so just a single to get
15 gal
left wide ball extra run now needed 7
runs Mahindra Insurance Brokers Ltd
MI BL 50 runs reached
excellent shot good fielding
in deep extra cover so one hit away for 2
6 runs keep the gleaming trophy ready for them
5.4
51 6
runs 14 balls left can captain finish off in
style will go for white
ball now fire required only
a
single now needed 4
runs will the
batsman hit the ball
across on this ball the over is over
so it's end of the over
single 6 over's play over 54 three runs now
in  12
balls MI BL Mahindra Insurance
Brokers Limited Now to lift the trophy
Just three runs away
in an automatic pass at
point now we can go
for four No still the silence before stumps
a
storm a big
hit Captain on strike now
needs two runs Can he finish in
style
this is sensible He is not in a hurry He does
not want to lose a wicket He has to score runs and
only now
needs one run A single run will be given Will win with a very
wide and that's it
Mahendra Insurance Brokers Limited The
Champions of ICC Lombard Brokers
Premier League
2025 MI
BL The Champions The
OG This is today's Baazigar Muqaddar ke Sikandar
Excellent congratulations
and very well played
Excellent batting performance Fielding
performance Excellent
performance Congratulations
to MI BL Mahindra Insurance Brokers
Limited This is today's Baazigar Today's Hero
Champions of ICC Lombard Brokers
Premier League 2025
Winner So wait for the presentation in some
time till the time stay tune Coming up
Presentation Party Will On The Party Will
On Masel Mit Solanki Will Continue Stay
Tune In The Game Of Life Stay Protected
With ICICI Lombard Health Insurance
Jump Full Colour Choice
Energy
Lo
In The Game Of Life Stay Protected With
ICICI Lombard Health Insurance Power Risto [Music] In
The Game Of Life Stay Protected With ICICI Lombard Health Insurance Junk Food Rang Ch
Energy Lo In The Game Of Life Stay Protected
With ICICI Lombard Health Insurance Power
Risto
[Music]
In The Game Of Life Stay Protected With
ICICI Lombard Health Insurance Junk
Food Rang
Ch Energy
Lo In The Game Of Life Stay Protected With
ICICI Lombard Health Insurance Power
Restoration
[Music]
You can join us Everyone
can join us Come quickly the
presentation party is on now
ok Thank you everyone and welcome to the
presentation party First of all make some
noises Round of applause Fantastic tournament
well
organised We played 28 matches in two days of
time ICICI Lombard Brokers Premier
League
2020 National and absolute good performance from all the
teams Once again a big round of applause
Many names are there but we will call some few
names and we will start I request
first of all all senior members to come
forward
just
ok fielding setting laga rhe
ok so I request the first of all
call the senior member from National Head make some noise
for Mr Sunny Bhardwaj can you please come forward before we
announce Man of the
Match National Head IC Lombard Insurance
Mr Himanshu Sharma Head
Zone I Lombard General Insurance and I request
Mr Gaurav Thakkar Head
Affinity thank you very much so
first of all make some noise to the
senior members these three pillars you can say
sowill start with man of the match very well
played excellent performance good fight
given an diesel and the team the final of
MIBL so MIBL the winner of the match final match
and man of the match any guesses man of the
match yes atli Arshad Ansari but no Arshad
Ansari is not Akash Lanjekar no of the
match a little twist
captain is done the
job 28 of 20 balls 14 and
so hard hitting make some noise
okay we have the next man of the
tournament we have some great counter there was many
names
but
finally the main and absolute good performance
with the ball with the bat any guess who is yes Arshad
Ansari the man of the
tournament maximum highest points and
man of the tournament Arshad
Ansari make some noise so now a
request runner up captain no diesel
to come
forward Rahul Panchal  Have some few
words once again excellent performance
very interesting performance strong performance so it was
very great tournament was very good
how did you like the final match your wicket
went in the first match no problem but you played
good fight and how are you feeling right now
feeling sad but great effort by the team
we played really well last year we last year we
last quarter final right but this year we
clifa for final and this achievement
thanks for team li thank you so much for our
effort come come
team
please come ok a lift trophy everyone sare aajayiye very
well played make some nash runner up of
ic
load pro kos premier league 2025 runner up
team na las aajayiye this
time this moment this golden moment
click the picture click the picture we have enough
space can go left a side more ok we go make some nash very well good
fight whole tournament n dazzlers ne kar diya hai
Kamal, thank you very much,
so once again make some noise, any hand moment,
any cheer up, something
special, okay, thank you very much,
runner, it's time now for the winner, a request,
Captain Akash Lanjekar, I have some few words
on
asking, okay, so winner Akash Lanjekar, I have some few
words, so how are you feeling,
sir, I am liking it very much, if we
talk about the team, then in our team, there is
Arshdeep Samal, Sandeep
Patil, Praful, they bowled very well,
Arshad has batted very well, in the
entire first and
last match of this tournament, he batted very well, the
entire overall team has fielded,
Nishigandh, Amit Lave, Chandresh, the entire
team has given team efforts, that is why we have
won this tournament today, thank you, so how was your
practice, now during office hours,
how did you take out time, what will be
the strategy at that time, I mean,
sometimes you got leave, sometimes you got free time, so
how was your practice and this is very
quality and something special, very  He has
bowled well, he has done a strong performance
for the MIPL team, so how was it and how did
you manage your time, I mean what was your strategy,
we practice in the morning at
7:00 am, we
book the ground here
for practice, we practice from 7:00 am to 8:30 am,
after that we
go to the office and get ready, that means the team
efforts are also of those people, that is
why it is done, so okay, okay,
thank you very much, so you will call the team
first before we call for the
final, so Mr. Sunny sir, we have some few
words to express the whole management and
how you feel, what was a crowd and how did
you like it, sir, I must, I must appreciate everyone
and I must appreciate some of the
families also, okay, we had super fun
in the last two days
starting from yesterday 8 am and ending
now we had super fun and I must
congratulate not only both of  These teams
but all the 18 teams who came here who really it was a very very hard
contest this
time and let me tell you this is the second
season of ICSC Lombard Brokers Premier
League and the bar is getting higher and higher I am sure
next year much more teams will come
and as I could speak to few of the teams they told us that
sir we are going to
practice very very hard for the coming year
so that is something I like that now
next year people will really practice and come hard so congratulations
to all thank
you Mr Sunny
Bhardwaj so call the team the champions come
it's time to lift the cup and
trophy so
Akash this is Messi K so he has some
special work captain will do
special work like Messi style
ok cameraman are you ready the
champions
make some run and
applause champions
IC Brokers
League the champions MIBL Mandra Insurance
Brokers Limited
ICSC Lombard Brokers Premier League
now we will have  some
photo ok it's the end of the
presentation party my cell friend Solanki
I am signing off let's see you next year and
thank you very much for joining
ok two one make some noise
one minute minute minute one more one more no more no more
ok thank you
in the game of life stay protected with
ICICI rd health insurance
jump food color
choice energy
low in the game of life stay protected with
ICICI rd health insurance power
[music]
risto aur